xcelr8.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - xcelr8.com

Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the www.xcelr8.com website. Your privacy and the integrity of any information you provide are important to us at www.xcelr8.com, the owner and operator of this website.

We have developed the following Privacy Policy for your protection.

This website is connected by “hyperlinks” to other third party sites. We are not responsible in any way for the privacy practices on other third party sites and suggest that you review the privacy policies on those linked sites before using them.

We are accountable for our Privacy Policy and our practices on our website, including the Privacy Policy as set out below. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please address them via e-mail to us via our “Contact Us” page.

What is Personal Information?  
Personal information is any piece of information about an identifiable individual. Personal information does include the name, title, business address, or business telephone number of an employee of an organization (“Personal Information”).

The terms “we”, “us” and “our” means www.xcelr8.com and its owner as designated herein. “You” and “your” means the individual who is a user.

What Information is Collected?  
We collect three kinds of information from our website:  
(1) your voluntarily provided Personal Information;  
(2) anonymous information about your visit; and,  
(3) “cookie” based information to help us track which pages on our websites you’re most interested in.

(1) Your Personal Information:  
During normal website usage, you can visit our site without communicating any personal information. However, to make use of certain features on our site, such as purchasing products, advertisements, promotions, contests, personalized services, paid subscriptions or newsletters, users may be asked to register with us.

As part of this voluntary registration, we may request contact information (such as name, mailing address, email address, etc.) and other data required for operating these services. We may only collect personal information from you if you voluntarily provide it. By voluntarily providing this personal information to us, by sending us a comment, suggestion or feedback, by entering a chatroom, blog or bulletin board, or by entering a contest or promotion that is posted on our site, you will be consenting to the collection, use and distribution of your personal information by us for the purposes set out herein. You are under no obligation to provide us with personal information to browse the public areas of our website, and you may access and enjoy many parts of our website without providing us any personal information.

Among other things, the following is a representative list of reasons we may ask for your personal information:

To run contests and promotions;  
To respond to your questions or the comments that you email to us;  
To provide you with newsletters or other subscription information;  
To distribute to sponsors and advertisers who run the promotions and/or for purposes of marketing by our sponsors and advertisers;  
To run chatrooms, blogs, discussion groups and bulletin boards;  
To gather aggregate information on website use and to provide services to the public of a general or specific nature, paid or unpaid.

(2) Anonymous Information About Your Visit:  
When you visit our site, information about your visit (e.g. how you navigate the site) may be collected and stored. This information may include the length of your visit, the date and time of your visit, the pages you look at and the sites you visit before and after leaving our site. It does not include personally identifiable information such as your name, mailing or email address or telephone number. We use this non-identifiable and aggregate information to better design our website. We also may share this information with our affiliates, suppliers, sponsors and advertisers. We collect the following non-identifiable information when you visit our website:

Your IP address  
Your Internet Service Provider (ISP)  
Your Web Browser

(3) Cookie”-Based Information:

To tailor our site to the needs and interests of our visitors, we keep track of the pages visited by our users by placing a small entry-in text file, called a “cookie”, on your hard drive. A cookie is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. Cookies do not reveal personal information. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself such as passwords, purchases and preferences. Cookies cannot read data from your hard drive.

You may visit the site with your cookies turned off. However, you may not be able to access some of the areas of our site, which require cookies for customization and personalization.

GOOGLE ADSENSE AND THE DOUBLECLICK DART COOKIE

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies. Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users’ activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, this website has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

How does the Privacy Policy deal with Children?  
This website is not lawfully accessible to persons under the age of 18 or who are otherwise covered by the provisions of the Child Online Privacy Act of 1998 (COPA). We will not knowingly encourage any minor to register with our site or to access those features which require registration. If a child has provided us with personal information, we ask that any concerned parent or guardian of the child contact us. Fraudulent use of this website may subject you to civil or criminal sanctions.

What if you do not agree with our Privacy Policy?  
By visiting our website and voluntarily providing personal information to the website, you agree to the terms of the online Terms of Use Agreement and this Privacy Policy. However, we welcome your comments and/or suggestions on improving our website and policies. If you do not agree to these terms, or wish to limit the use of any of your personal information that we may have, you may contact us via email at our “Contact Us” page. In the case of promotions, we will occasionally ask if you consent to the forwarding of Personal Information to our promotional and advertising partners. You may confirm or decline your consent.

As a function of our fulfilling certain legal requirements, we may disclose Personal Information without consent.

We will retain Personal Information only as long as is required for the purposes we describe and as is required under law. Once Personal Information is no longer required (or if you have opted-out or withdrawn your consent), it is our practice that it is destroyed, deleted or made anonymous.

All decisions we make involving Personal Information are based on accurate, complete and up-to-date information. We rely on you, however, to disclose all material information and to inform us of any relevant changes or corrections as they may relate to you. We encourage you to contact us as soon as possible, and we will make the appropriate reasonable corrections or amendments, upon receipt of appropriate evidence.

We will protect Personal Information with appropriate safeguards and security measures. We utilize a combination of physical, administrative and electronic measures to ensure Personal Information is adequately protected on a day-to-day basis, for storage and disposal.

If you send us an email message that includes Personal Information, we will use that information to respond to your inquiry. Please note that email is not necessarily secure against interception.

We reserve the right to add, modify or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time and in our sole discretion.
